<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Escaping Perfection</title>
    <link>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Escaping Perfection</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 01:06:19 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Whoops</title>
      <link>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/post/whoops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 01:06:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/post/whoops/</guid>
      <description>Work has caused this site to get away from me. But I think I have learned something in the weeks that I haven&amp;rsquo;t written here. I have undervalued the storytelling ability of lyrics and song. Since I was young, I&amp;rsquo;ve had ideas of stories I wish to wrote, some about other times, some about other planets. But what I only recently realized is that the story wasn&amp;rsquo;t as important to me as the message I wanted to convey, and the way I wished to convey it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Unlikely Encounter</title>
      <link>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/post/encounter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 22:36:27 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/post/encounter/</guid>
      <description>My favorite form of art takes some people by surprise. It&amp;rsquo;s not music, or painting, or sculpture, it&amp;rsquo;s the art of games. Sometimes people ask me why, and how games can even be considered art. Ignoring the shallowness of the question, I usually answer that games are the art of laws. Music uses sound to convey thoughts, paintings uses paint, and games use rules. I actually find rules to be the most effective, and direct way to invoke thoughts or emotions in others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Introduction</title>
      <link>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/post/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:45:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/post/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Its rather late tonight, but I think its a perfect time to finally introduce myself. You may call me Absurd Abstract, Absurd, A, or anything inbetween. I am not entirely sure if this website works, or where it reaches, but here I work as a asseser of technologies. If you are reading this from another planet, world, or timeline, my job is basically to edit the outputs of computational intelligence software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning As We Go</title>
      <link>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/post/learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:21:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/post/learning/</guid>
      <description>It is a goal of mine to share some nugget of progress every day. I guess todays progress is the creation of this website itself. &amp;ldquo;Escaping Perfection.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;I hope you aren&amp;rsquo;t expecting anything of high quality on this page. I will go into further detail on my intended message later, but the pursuit of high quality goes against my beliefs. This site will soon be filled with convaluded link chains, horrible drawings, strange sounds, and mind twisting stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorry to nobody</title>
      <link>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/post/briefappology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 14:56:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://absurdabstract.escapingperfection.github.io/post/briefappology/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s ironic that in the process of embarking on this journey, I almost seperated myself from its purpose. To you, the reader, there would&amp;rsquo;ve been no difference whether I made this post or held off posting this site for another day. However, holding off the sharing of thoughts is the very thing that goes against this sites fundamental philosophy. Waiting. Hesitating. Perfecting&amp;hellip;&#xA;I will go into further detail when I have more time to formulate my thoughts.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
